nyulangone.org 2019-12-04

# Digital Privacy Statement | NYU Langone Health

NYU Langone Health is committed to respecting your digital privacy. This privacy statement applies to the collection and use of information related to our public websites: [https://nyulangone.org](https://nyulangone.org/), [https://med.nyu.edu](https://med.nyu.edu/), and [https://medli.nyu.edu](https://medli.nyu.edu/).

## Personally Identifiable Information

NYU Langone public websites do not collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit, unless you voluntarily provide us with that information.

However, you can choose to submit personally identifiable information to us, such as by inputting your information to join a mailing list. NYU Langone may use that information for such purposes as fulfilling your requests for our information or services, communicating information that may be of interest to you, and conducting research surveys.

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

When you visit NYU Langone websites, we automatically collect and store non-personally identifiable information such as data sent by your web browser, including the internet address of your computer (IP address) in server logs.

We also collect standard information about your computer, such as your web browser and operating system, and about your usage of our websites, such as pages visited, length of visit, and search queries. This information, which does not identify you personally, is aggregated and used to help diagnose problems and suggest areas for improving our websites.

## Cookies

Like many websites, portions of NYU Langone’s websites use cookies.

Cookies are text files that may be transferred to your computer or mobile device through your web browsing software. These cookies are used to remember your preferences or to track statistics on usage of various portions of NYU Langone websites. Our use of cookies does not involve the collection of personally identifiable information.

You can choose not to accept cookies by selecting settings on your web browser that block or restrict the use of cookies. You can also delete cookies that have been placed on your computer or device.

## Sharing Your Information

NYU Langone may collect and maintain personally identifiable information (PII) about you, as described above. However, we will not sell, rent, or share that PII. NYU Langone will use your PII only as is permitted under institutional policies and in compliance with federal and state laws and regulations.

## Behavioral Advertising

NYU Langone may contract with third-party vendors to show our advertisements on non-NYU Langone websites and digital properties. NYU Langone and third-party vendors with whom we contract may use cookies and web beacons to serve our ads based on your prior visit or visits to NYU Langone websites and to assess the effectiveness of our ads. This is also called “targeted advertising” or “interest-based advertising.” These techniques use only non-personally identifiable information.

## Security

NYU Langone has implemented reasonable physical, technical, and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure all information we collect online against loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control.

Please note that while we always attempt to protect the security of your information, NYU Langone cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted through our websites.

## Third-Party Sites

NYU Langone websites may link to external sites that are not controlled by NYU Langone.

NYU Langone is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those external websites, and does not make any representations as to the adequacy of their privacy and security practices.

## Changes and Questions

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement in whole or in part at any time.

If you have questions about this privacy statement or the privacy practices of NYU Langone websites, please contact [webteam@nyumc.org](mailto:webteam@nyumc.org).
